<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<collection>
  <description>Some recipes used in the XML tutorial. </description>

  <recipe>
    <title>Beef Parmesan with Garlic Pasta</title>

    <ingredient amount="1.5" name="beef in cubes" unit="pound"/>

    <ingredient amount="1" name="onion, sliced thin"/>

    <ingredient amount="1" name="seasoned bread crumbs" unit="cup"/>

    <ingredient amount="0.5" name="parmesan cheese" unit="cup"/>

    <ingredient amount="2" name="olive oil" unit="tablespoon"/>

    <ingredient amount="1" name="spaghetti sauce" unit="cup"/>

    <ingredient amount="12" name="pasta" unit="ounce"/>

    <ingredient amount="2" name="garlic sauce" unit="teaspoon"/>

    <preparation>
      <step>Preheat oven to 375 degrees F.</step>

      <step>Coat meat with the bread crumbs and parmesan cheese.</step>

      <step>Heat olive oil in a large frying pan, put 1 teaspoon of the garlic
      sauce and mix it for 3 minutes. Quick fry meat.</step>

      <step>Place meat in a casserole baking dish. Place onion rings on top of
      meat.</step>

      <step>Bake at 375 degrees F for 20 to 35 minutes, depending on the
      thickness of the meat. Sprinkle mozzarella over meat and leave in the
      oven till bubbly.</step>

      <step>Boil pasta al dente. Drain, and toss in 1 teaspoon garlic sauce.
      For a stronger garlic taste, season with garlic powder. Top with grated
      parmesan and parsley for color. Serve meat and sauce on top of
      pasta!</step>
    </preparation>

    <comment>Make the meat ahead of time, and refrigerate over
    night.</comment>

    <nutrition calories="1167" carbohydrates="45" fat="23" protein="32"/>
  </recipe>

  <recipe>
    <title>Ricotta Pie</title>

    <ingredient name="filling">
      <ingredient amount="3" name="ricotta cheese" unit="pound"/>

      <ingredient amount="12" name="eggs"/>

      <ingredient amount="2" name="white sugar" unit="cup"/>

      <ingredient amount="2" name="vanilla extract" unit="teaspoon"/>

      <ingredient amount="0.25" name="semisweet chocolate chips" unit="cup"/>

      <preparation>
        <step>Beat all the eggs, 2 cups sugar and vanilla extract together.
        Stir in the ricotta cheese and the chocolate chips. Set aside.</step>
      </preparation>
    </ingredient>

    <ingredient name="dough">
      <ingredient amount="4" name="all purpose flour" unit="cup"/>

      <ingredient amount="5" name="baking powder" unit="teaspoon"/>

      <ingredient amount="1" name="white sugar" unit="cup"/>

      <ingredient amount="0.5" name="shortening" unit="cup"/>

      <ingredient amount="4" name="eggs, lightly beaten"/>

      <ingredient amount="1" name="vanilla extract" unit="teaspoon"/>

      <preparation>
        <step>Combine the flour, baking powder, and 1 cup of the sugar
        together. Cut in the shortening and mix until the mixture resembles
        coarse crumbs. Mix in 4 of the eggs and 1 teaspoon of the vanilla.
        Divide dough into 4 balls and chill (if needed).</step>
      </preparation>
    </ingredient>

    <ingredient amount="*" name="milk"/>

    <preparation>
      <step>Preheat oven to 325 degrees F. Grease two deep dish pie
      plates.</step>

      <step>Roll out 2 of the balls to fit into the pie pans. Do not make the
      crust too thick as it will expand during cooking and get too thick. Do
      not flute the edges of the dough. Roll out the other 2 balls of dough
      and cut each into 8 narrow strips for the top of the crust.</step>

      <step>Pour the filling evenly into the pie crusts. Top each pie with 8
      narrow strips of dough or cookie cut-outs. Brush top of pie with milk
      for shine. Place foil on the edge of crust. </step>

      <step>Bake at 325 degrees F for 20 to 30 minutes then remove foil.
      Continue to bake for another 25 or 30 minutes or until a knife inserted
      in the center comes out clean.</step>
    </preparation>

    <nutrition calories="349" carbohydrates="64" fat="18" protein="18"/>
  </recipe>
</collection>
